Se parece a ti
forgot something this morning.
Care to take it?
This is inappropriate, Meg.
Oh, come on.
Since when did fun
become inappropriate for you?
Miss Rose is here to see you.
Take her out of here.
Excuse me, which one?
So, that's it?
You’re trading a...
gorgeous woman
for some street puppy?
Is that your final
decision, Walt?
Sorry.
Sit.
Okay, thanks.
Seems like you’re
a popular...
boy.
Why do you need me?
Oh, Meg?
She’s too materialistic.
My father sees right
through women like her.
You, on the other hand,
he actually liked you,
Curly Pie.
And what exactly do
I have to do at that
Christmas dinner?
We need to pretend
we’re fond of each other.
And most importantly
convince my father of it.
It won’t be easy,
Curly Pie.
I'm in.
Nice.